Florencia Guadalupe Gonzalez

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

+54 9 11 23965730 florsg44713@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Redux

Node.js

Express

Postgres

Sequelize

Scrum

Lenguages

Spanish - Native

English - B2/C1

German - Basic

Hobbies

- Volunteer at animal shelters
- Reading books.
- Trading and investing.

Summary

A 18 years old fast learner, hard worker, and team player web developer with solid experience and confidence in her skills that's seeking a job to improve even more as a rising professional and provide agile solutions using React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, and Sequelize among others.

Employment History

Developer experience on freelance projects

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

Most of my programming projects were done by using all the technologies mentioned above in my summary across multiple APIs, third-party integrations, and databases.

Since they were personal projects I had to do the frontend, backend, and the DB.

Some of those projects are:

-WeatherApp: A weather forecast application that you can use to look at the weather conditions in real-time all around the globe, also gives you detailed information about the city you searched.

Currently working on geolocalization integration and an interactive map.

MoviesApp: It allows you to discover, search and view details of +5000 movies, either old ones and new releases. It also let you watch the trailers of every movie in stored in our Database.

PokeApp: Basically a Pokedex. It's a pokemon wiki will let you do, search for pokemon, see their stats and types, and also create a new pokemon.

Teaching Assistant for fullstack development students

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Teaching Assistants always work on pairs so we were a team during our instance as TA's. Our main responsabilities:

- \bullet Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.

Education

Full-stack web developer certificate. Henry Academy Bootcamp

NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

An intensive programming Bootcamp in which I learned a lot about both web development and teamwork in where I developed many personal and requested projects. This Bootcamp gave me approximately 850 hours of coding.